[
    {
      "question": "Microsoft Office is an example of a?",
      "correct_answer": "Horizontal market software",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Closed source software",
        "Open source software",
        "vertical  software"
      ]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "Which company developed 'Hack' Programming Language?",
      "correct_answer": "Facebook",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Google",
        "Microsoft",
        "Apple"
      ]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "Which programming language is developed by James A Gosling?",
      "correct_answer": "Java",
      "incorrect_answers": ["ASP.Net", "PHP", "C#"]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "C Programming language was developed by ___________.",
      "correct_answer": "Dennis Ritchie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Charles Babbage",
        " Larry Wall",
        " James Gosling"
      ]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "Who invented JavaScript the programming language?",
      "correct_answer": " Brendan Eich",
      "incorrect_answers": [" George Eastman", " Emil Erlenmeyer", "Willem Einthoven"]
    },
    {
     
      "question": "Which among the following is not an Object Oriented Programming Language?",
      "correct_answer": "PASCAL",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Python", "Java", " C++"]
    },
    {
    
      "question": "Which of the following is not a computer programming language?",
      "correct_answer": "NULL",
      "incorrect_answers": ["PYTHON", "JAVA", "BASIC"]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "Which is a reserved word in the java programming language?",
      "correct_answer": "Keyword",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Identifier","Variable","Main"]
    },
    {
      "question": "HTML stands for",
      "correct_answer": "Hyper Text MarkUp language",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hyper Text MarksUp language","Hyper Tells MarkUp language","Hyper Text MakeUp language"]
    },
    {
      "question": "CSS stands for",
      "correct_answer": "Cascading style sheet",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Cascading styled sheet","Cascading style service","Common style sheet"]
    }
   
  ]
  